♪Minum ibun♪
♪最小伊文♪
♪Your roots are holding tight♪
♪你的根紧紧抓住♪
♪On this land♪
♪在这片土地上♪
♪Mengejar ombak♪
♪门格贾尔·姆巴克♪
♪My leaves fly by♪
♪我的树叶飞过♪
♪The border of thousands of stones♪
♪数千块石头的边界♪
♪Looking at each other from afar♪
♪远远地看着对方♪
♪The edge of the cliff is♪
♪悬崖的边缘是♪
♪Live together forever♪
♪永远在一起♪
♪When we meet and part again♪
♪当我们再次相遇又分开的时候♪
♪When we depend on each other and are far away♪
♪当我们相依为命 而疏远时♪
♪I never forget♪
♪我永远不会忘记♪
♪The light reflected on the sword and knife♪
♪剑和刀上反射的光♪
♪Light up the dim sky♪
♪照亮昏暗的天空♪
♪Abandoned dreams♪
♪被遗弃的梦想♪
♪Shattered in the wind♪
♪被风吹碎♪
♪Against the direction of the wind and waves♪
♪逆着风浪的方向♪
♪See thousands of ships crossing♪
♪看到成千上万的船只穿越♪
♪This world changes♪
♪这个世界改变了♪
♪A suit of armor with make-up swinging in the wind♪
♪妆容随风 摇曳的铠甲♪
♪Drinking ice, the blood is hard to be cold, dreaming of having fun in love♪
♪喝冰，血难凉， 梦想着恋爱的乐趣♪
♪Just wish you were by my side♪
♪只希望 你在我身边♪
♪Don't waste spring time♪
♪别浪费春天的时光♪
♪Trees reach the sky, roots connect, your friends uphold justice in the world♪
♪树参天，根相连， 朋友主持天下正义♪
♪Seeing the light flickering on the shoulder♪
♪看到肩膀上闪烁的光芒♪
♪No regrets in this world♪
♪这世上没有遗憾♪
=Wonderland of Love=
=爱的仙境=
=Episode 23=
=第23集=
Ayah.
呀呀。
I offered a drink to say congratulations to my father.
我敬了一杯酒， 向父亲表示祝贺。
After drinking,
喝完之后，
me and Ying will
我和莹会
get married
结婚了
Drink it.
喝吧。
The commander-in-chief is aware.
总司令是知道的。
Of.
的。
Good.
好的。
He was aware.
他知道。
Commander.
指挥官。
Controller.
控制器。
Bind this rebellious child.
束缚这个叛逆的孩子。
Commander.
指挥官。
The poison in the father's body has not been offered.
父亲体内的毒还没有献出来。
He was still confused.
他仍然很困惑。
Controller.
控制器。
Send him back to the room.
送他回房间。
- Young master.
- 少爷。
Rebellious child.
叛逆的孩子。
Didn't think so
没想到如此
you will mistreat father.
你会虐待父亲。
Young master!
少爷！
Be careful, commander-in-chief!
小心点，总司令！
Great Commander!
伟大的指挥官！
Young master!
少爷！
What is the reason?
是什么原因？
Are there any misunderstandings?
是不是有什么误会？
Yes, young master.
是的，少爷。
This is the commander in chief, young master.
这是总司令，少爷。
The commander-in-chief was confused.
总司令一头雾水。
Quickly grab his sword
赶紧拿起他的剑
so that he doesn't hurt himself.
以免他伤害自己。
Dream it.
做梦。
He is the commander in chief.
他是总司令。
Be careful, commander-in-chief!
小心点，总司令！
Great Commander!
伟大的指挥官！
Young master!
少爷！
Are there any misunderstandings?
是不是有什么误会？
Great Commander!
伟大的指挥官！
Who dares to hurt the commander-in-chief?
谁敢 伤总司令？
Be careful!
当心！
We will get married later.
我们稍后会结婚。
Don't hurt my wife.
不要伤害我的妻子。
who is your wife
谁是你的妻子
Shu, stop!
舒，站住！
Orang Jieshuo.
Orang Jieshuo.
The young master let the Jieshuo people sneak in on the pretext of marriage.
少爷以 联姻为借口，让界朔人潜入。
We trusted him in vain.
我们徒劳地信任他。
Young Master Cui.
崔少爷。
Do not try to escape.
不要试图逃跑。
Mr. Shiqi has already said.
士奇先生已经说过了。
Yes
是的
not Young Master Cui.
不是崔少爷。
Namanya Liu Chengfeng.
Namanya Liu Chengfeng.
It's not wrong to call him Tuan Muda Cui.
叫他团木达崔也没有错。
Now, he was still disguising himself as Young Master Cui.
现在，他依然伪装 成崔公子。
Namun, namanya Liu Chengfeng.
Namun, namanya Liu Chengfeng.
Young Master Cui.
崔少爷。
Liu Chengfeng.
Liu Chengfeng.
Liu Cheng...
Liu Cheng...
Rebellious child.
叛逆的孩子。
How dare you conspire with the Jieshuo people.
竟敢 与界朔人勾结。
Have you
你
forget
忘记
Cui Family revenge?
崔家报仇？
Cui Yi!
Cui Yi!
The situation has become like this.
情况就变成这样了。
Do not pretend
别假装
be a loving father.
做一个慈爱的父亲。
I asked you.
我问过你。
Have you ever been sincere?
你曾经真诚过吗？
You once considered me
你曾经考虑过我
as your own child sincerely?
真心当自己的孩子吗？
You're just using me.
你只是在利用我。
What does it matter?
有什么关系？
grudge between the Cui Family and Jieshuo
崔家与杰硕的恩怨
with me?
与我一起？
Okay.
好的。
I have no son.
我没有儿子。
I only have one daughter.
我只有一个女儿。
Ying.
莹。
You don't have to
你不必
keep your identity a secret again.
再次对您的身份保密。
All.
全部。
This is my daughter.
这是我的女儿。
He is the real Cui Lin.
他才是真正的崔霖。
He too
他也是
using the name Cui Lin
使用崔琳这个名字
in a military camp.
在一个军营里。
I also always considered him as my own son.
我也一直把他当作 自己的儿子。
Today, he brought in our enemies
今天，他带来了我们的敌人
and don't want to be my child anymore.
并且不想再成为我的孩子了。
So,
所以，
I only have one daughter.
我只有一个女儿。
Cui Lin
Cui Lin
my only child
我唯一的孩子
However, he is greater
然而，他更伟大
of men in this world.
这个世界上的男人。
Liu Chengfeng.
Liu Chengfeng.
Since you colluded with Jieshuo,
既然 你和杰硕勾结，
poison me,
毒害我，
rebel and bring in enemies,
叛逆并引入敌人，
you are unfaithful, immoral and disobedient.
你不忠、 不道德、不听话。
Your crime has been revealed.
你的罪行已经被揭露了。
Give up quickly!
赶紧放弃吧！
You remember
你记得
can you catch me today?
今天你能抓住我吗？
There is a blue light on the arrow head.
箭头上有蓝色的光芒。
Presumably it was coated with poison.
想必是被涂上了毒药。
Li Ni.
李妮.
Your identity limits you
你的身份限制了你
to bring in the military.
引进军队。
You are just a few people
你们只是少数人
can catch me?
能抓住我吗？
I want to kill you.
我想杀了你。
- Dad! - Commander in chief!
- 爸爸！ ——总司令！
Dad, are you okay?
爸爸，你还好吗？
It's fine.
没关系。
Do not worry.
不用担心。
The Zhenxi army was outside the city.
镇西军在城外。
If we fight again,
如果我们再吵架
both parties will definitely suffer huge losses.
双方肯定都会 遭受巨大的损失。
Lepaskan Liu Chengfeng.
Lepaskan Liu Chengfeng.
Go away from here!
离开这里！
Shiqi.
Shiqi.
Your men are hiding to ambush outside the city.
你的人正躲在 城外埋伏。
Liu Chengfeng had already brought people out of the city.
柳乘风已经 带人出城了。
You can attack them.
你可以攻击他们。
Slowly.
慢慢地。
Ayah.
呀呀。
I told Taozi to check dad's pulse.
我叫桃子 给爸爸把脉。
No need.
不需要。
Dad, it's okay.
爸爸，没关系。
Taozi has already said.
桃子已经说过了。
He himself provided this antidote.
他亲自提供了这种解药。
Poison will be offered slowly.
毒药会 慢慢提供。
It's good, father, don't fight.
很好，爸爸，别吵架了。
When father found out this was the crime of the disobedient son,
当父亲发现 这是不听话的儿子犯下的罪时，
Dad couldn't help himself.
爸爸无法自拔。
I didn't think he conspired with Jieshuo.
我不认为 他与杰硕合谋。
He knew the Cui Family
他认识崔家
berdendam dengan Jieshuo.
berdendam dengan Jieshuo.
I don't know why
我不知道为什么
he became like this.
他变成了这个样子。
It was in vain that his father thought of him as his biological son
父亲视 他为亲生儿子，也是枉然
many years.
很多年。
Ayah,
啊呀，
don't be sad anymore.
别再伤心了。
Ying,
英，
after your father and mother have been married for ten years,
你的父亲和母亲 结婚十年后，
you were just born.
你刚刚出生。
Although father announced
虽然父亲宣布
you are a man
你是一个男人
so that the government does not grant the father another wife,
这样政府 就不会再给父亲另一个妻子，
your father and mother
你的父亲和母亲
have a selfish mind,
有一颗 自私的心，
that is, we want to leave everything in the Cui Family
也就是我们要 留下崔家的一切
to you.
给你。
Only sons are important in this world.
这个世界上只有儿子才是重要的。
No daughter ever inherits the family property,
没有女儿 继承家产，
especially in the military.
尤其是在军队中。
We announce you are a boy
我们宣布你是个男孩
for you
为你
can have everything in the Cui Family.
可以拥有崔家的一切。
I understand, father.
我明白了，父亲。
Ever since I was sensible,
自从我懂事以来，
father told me
父亲告诉我
about this clearly.
关于这一点说得很清楚。
This is my choice too.
这也是我的选择。
I don't find it difficult.
我觉得不难。
Sadly.
可悲的是。
Sama ada Liu Chengfeng
Sama ada Liu Chengfeng
or Cui Li,
or Cui Li,
how nice
多好
if they can help you.
如果他们可以帮助你。
The human mind is unpredictable.
人心是不可预测的。
Even though dad was alert,
尽管爸爸很警觉，
appear
出现
a traitor at last.
最后成了叛徒
Ayah.
呀呀。
Dad has done a lot for me.
爸爸为我做了 很多事。
Ying.
莹。
Dad revealed your identity today.
爸爸今天透露了你的身份 。
I am afraid that many more problems will be caused in the future.
恐怕 未来还会引发更多的问题。
I know you are wise and do not hesitate.
我知道你很聪明 ，不会犹豫。
You are better than anyone else.
你比任何人都好。
As a father,
作为一名父亲，
Dad is still worried.
爸爸还是很担心。
If dad doesn't take good care of you,
如果爸爸没有好好照顾你
What kind of
什么样的
father want to face your late mother later?
爸爸以后想见 你已故的妈妈吗？
Ayah,
啊呀，
do not worry.
不用担心。
I am my father's son.
我是我父亲的儿子。
Although many problems will befall me,
虽然 很多问题都会降临到我身上，
finished?
完成的？
I am
我是
will not be shackled by the worldly.
不会被世俗所束缚。
Good to say you.
很高兴说你。
Now it's different.
现在情况不同了。
Even though everyone
尽管大家
find our clause,
找到我们的条款，
we are children
我们是孩子
no need to be afraid
无需害怕
Of.
的。
Don't worry, dad.
别担心，爸爸。
Greetings to the young lady.
向这位年轻女士问好。
Greetings to the commanders.
向指挥官们问好。
During the old days,
过去的日子里，
the government insists on giving me another wife
政府坚持要 再给我一个妻子
because I have no children.
因为我没有孩子。
The love between me and my wife is deep.
我和我妻子之间的爱 是深厚的。
After we gave birth to a daughter,
生下 女儿后，
I said I got a son.
我说 我有儿子了。
Then, the situation in the draw changed.
随后，抽签的情况发生了变化。
So, I didn't tell you
所以，我没有告诉你
about the truth.
关于真相。
Actually, Cui Lin is my only daughter.
其实，崔琳 是我唯一的女儿。
Oh it's like that.
哦，是这样的。
Even if you are young
即使你还年轻
holding the position of lieutenant only,
只担任中尉职务，
we watched
我们看了
his personal performance.
他的个人表现。
Women are equal to men.
女性与男性平等。
We will definitely try our best to help him.
我们一定会尽力 帮助他。
We will definitely obey.
我们一定会服从的。
Don't worry, commander in chief.
别担心，总司令。
Me and Junior Commander Pei
我和裴少帅
hide outside the city according to your instructions.
按照你的指示躲到城外。
Kami memang nampak Liu Chengfeng
Kami memang nampak Liu Chengfeng
membawa orang Jieshuo.
membawa orang Jieshuo.
We ambushed him when he was not ready.
我们 趁他还没准备好时伏击了他。
However,
然而，
their poison is too great.
他们的毒太大了。
Even though many people are attacked,
尽管很多人受到攻击，
Liu Chengfeng
Liu Chengfeng
still managed to escape.
还是成功逃脱了。
He's lost his mind.
他失去了理智。
In fact, he conspired with the enemy.
事实上，他与敌人密谋。
Jieshuo pandai menggunakan racun.
Jieshuo pandai menggunakan racun.
Later, we must be careful.
以后我们一定要小心。
Of.
的。
That's Lieutenant He, right?
那是何中尉吧？
Not.
不是。
Young Miss Cui has arrived.
崔小姐来了。
Young Miss Cui is already struggling.
崔小姐已经陷入困境了。
Brother Bao is already struggling.
宝哥已经很挣扎了。
We are our own people.
我们是我们自己的人。
Tentera Zhenxi
Tentera Zhenxi
willing to help Ms. Young Cui eliminate the enemy.
愿意帮助年轻的崔女士 消灭敌人。
I circulated first.
我先传了。
The young lady and Mr. Shiqi are chatting.
小姐和十七先生正在聊天。
Fortunately you are here today.
幸运的是你今天在这里。
We are our own people.
我们是我们自己的人。
Tentera Zhenxi
Tentera Zhenxi
willing to help Ms. Young Cui eliminate the enemy.
愿意帮助年轻的崔女士 消灭敌人。
I'm willing too.
我也愿意。
Brash mouth.
傲慢的嘴。
Bao said earlier,
鲍先生之前说过，
they had already wiped out many Jieshuo people.
他们已经消灭了 不少界朔人。
However, Liu Chengfeng managed to escape.
然而， 柳乘风却成功逃脱。
Tak sangka Liu Chengfeng bersubahat dengan Jieshuo.
Tak sangka Liu Chengfeng bersubahat dengan Jieshuo.
Keluarga Cui dan Jieshuo
Keluarga Cui dan Jieshuo
hold a grudge
记仇
From now on,
今后，
he's not my brother anymore
他不再是我兄弟了
He is an enemy of the Cui Family.
他是崔家的敌人。
I shouldn't say that,
我不应该这么说
But
但
after hearing this, i feel relieved.
听了这话， 我心里释然了。
You haven't told me yet.
你还没告诉我呢。
How did you find out my father was poisoned.
你怎么知道 我父亲中毒了？
How did you find it?
你是怎样找到它的？
rancangan Liu Chengfeng
rancangan Liu Chengfeng
and cooperate with my father?
并与我父亲合作？
After I returned to camp,
当我回到营地后，
I thought about this.
我想到了这一点。
The more I think, the more I feel there is something unfamiliar.
越想越觉得 有什么陌生的地方。
So, Taozi and I sneaked into the Cui Residence
于是，我和桃子 偷偷溜进了崔宅
to investigate the commander-in-chief
调查总司令
exposed to what poison?
接触了什么毒？
Er Duo, control it well so that other people don't notice.
二朵，控制好 ，别让别人发现。
Taozi is very confident
桃子很有信心
Panglima besar terkena racun Jieshuo.
Panglima besar terkena racun Jieshuo.
Kebetulan awak terkena racun Jieshuo juga.
Kebetulan awak terkena racun Jieshuo juga.
At that time, you saw Liu Chengfeng.
那时， 你看到了柳乘风。
So, I suspect
所以，我怀疑
the incident of the commander-in-chief being poisoned has something to do with him.
统帅中毒的事件， 跟他有关系。
At first, the commander-in-chief
起初，总司令
refused to believe it.
拒绝相信。
Until then,
直到那时，
he found it was indeed his crime.
他发现这确实是他的罪行。
My father was very sad.
我父亲非常伤心。
my lord
我的主
No need to be so polite.
没必要这么客气。
Do you know about it?
你知道吗？
I mean my lord...
我的意思是我的主人...
Everyone knows that
大家都知道
Cui Yi
Cui Yi
have a son.
有一个儿子。
(Empress, Lu) Try to guess what happened.
（吕后） 你猜猜发生了什么事。
This boy is not his.
这个男孩不是他的。
Not his son?
不是他儿子？
That's right.
这是正确的。
He has only one daughter.
他只有 一个女儿。
Since childhood, he was raised as a boy.
从小， 他就被当男孩养大。
His daughter disguised herself as a man
他的女儿 女扮男装
and served in the Cui Family Army.
并 在崔家军服役。
Apparently, he is famous.
显然，他很有名。
What's his name?
他叫什么名字？
Leftenan He.
左赫特南.
I didn't think something like this existed.
我不认为有这样的事情存在。
Cui Yi
Cui Yi
cheating beta
作弊测试版
However, the employees at the hall said seriously,
然而，大厅的工作人员却严肃地说：
Cui Yi is very powerful.
崔毅很厉害。
Furthermore, Sun Jing
此外，孙静
not dead and still conquering the Tong Border,
还没死 ，还在征服塘边，
an important military base.
重要的军事基地。
Again,
再次，
Cui Yi merampas
Cui Yi merampas
Changzhou now.
现在常州。
So, the officers
那么，官员们
advise beta
建议测试版
to calm Cui Yi's heart.
让崔毅的心平静下来。
A good idea
一个好主意
crossed my mind.
我想到了。
My lord wants...
主人想要...
Cui Yi doesn't have a son, right?
崔毅没有儿子吧？
Beta helps him find an adoptive child.
贝塔帮助他 找到了一个收养的孩子。
Until then,
直到那时，
The Cui family has an heir.
崔氏家族有继承人。
So, Commander Cui
我知道，崔司令
will listen to beta instructions later.
稍后会听 beta 说明。
my lord
我的主
Who do you want to choose as the heir of the Cui Family?
你想选谁 作为崔家的继承人？
That's why I came to meet my sister.
这就是我 来见我姐姐的原因。
Beta wants to choose one
贝塔想要选择一个
from your sister's niece
来自你姐姐的侄女
to become the adopted son of the Cui Family.
成为崔家的养子。
my lord,
我的主，
I'm afraid this is not good.
恐怕这不太好。
Why?
为什么？
Don't you want to?
你不想吗？
It's not that you don't want to.
并不是你不想。
Try to think.
尝试思考一下。
Cui Yi Panglima Besar Pingliang,
Cui Yi Panglima Besar Pingliang,
the commander in chief of the Cui Family Army.
崔家军总司令。
In that year,
在那年，
he led an army to conquer Jieshuo.
he led an army to conquer Jieshuo.
You have heard
你听说过
the greatness of Commander-in-Chief Cui.
崔总司令的伟大。
This kind of person
这种人
refused to retreat from Changzhou.
不肯撤出常州。
It is obvious that he cannot be controlled by the government.
很明显，他不能被 政府控制。
Even though my lord has good intentions
纵然吾主本意是好的
to choose an heir for his side,
为自己一方选择继承人，
sister worried about his opinion,
姐姐担心他的意见，
my lord
我的主
wanted to seize the Cui Family's property
想要夺取崔家的财产
and military power against the Cui Family Army.
以及对抗崔家军的军事力量。
Beta really thinks so.
贝塔确实是这么认为的。
After all.
毕竟。
There was no way Cui Yi could have guessed that.
崔易怎么也猜不到这一点。
Cui Yi had been leading the military for many years .
崔毅领导军队多年。
He asked his daughter to disguise herself as a boy.
他要求他的女儿 把自己伪装成男孩。
In fact, his daughter is wise.
事实上，他的女儿很聪明。
Now, he revealed this.
现在，他透露了这一点。
It is impossible that he intended to find an heir.
他不可能是想 寻找继承人。
Impossible
不可能的
he could not guess my master's thoughts.
他猜不透我主人的想法。
If so, how?
如果是这样，怎么办？
Should I accept Cui Yi's daughter ?
我该 接受崔毅的女儿吗？
as an adopted child?
作为一个被收养的孩子？
Then, appointed her as a princess.
然后，册封她为公主。
After she became a princess,
当她成为公主后，
find him a husband who obeys his word?
给他找 一个言出必行的丈夫？
Is it like this?
是这样吗？
new beta can be ordered
可以订购新测试版
The Cui Family Army?
崔家军？
Cui Yi's daughter
崔毅的女儿
raised like a man.
像个男人一样长大。
Presumably,
想必，
he's not an ordinary person.
他不是一个普通人。
Sister is worried that she refuses to be a princess.
姐姐担心 她拒绝当公主。
If she refuses to be a princess,
如果她拒绝成为公主
what does he want to be?
他想成为什么？
This is just a guess.
这只是一个猜测。
If my lord has this plan,
陛下若有此计，
It's good, sir, to send someone
先生，派人来真是太好了
to find out
找出来
Young Miss Cui's thoughts.
崔小姐的想法。
See if she wants to be a princess.
看看 她愿不愿意当公主。
Ayah.
呀呀。
Sit down.
坐下。
In today's series hall,
在今天的系列大厅里，
the occurrence of a matter.
某件事的发生。
Cui Lin, son of Cui Yi
Cui Lin, son of Cui Yi
is a girl.
是一个女孩。
What?
什么？
Cui Yi only has one daughter.
崔一只有一个 女儿。
However, he lied
然而他撒了谎
that she had a son,
她有一个儿子，
namely Cui Lin.
也就是崔琳。
Later, he received an adopted child.
后来， 他收养了一个孩子。
This adopted child
这个领养的孩子
using the name Cui Lin.
使用崔琳这个名字。
His daughter as well
他的女儿也是如此
uses the surname He.
使用何姓。
He was famous in the Cui Family Army.
他在崔家军中赫赫有名。
He was known as Lieutenant He.
他被称为何中尉。
Apparently Lieutenant He
显然是何中尉
Cui Yi's daughter.
崔毅之女。
It should be.
它应该是。
Do you still remember?
你还记得吗？
Before this, the King of Qin
在此之前，秦王
sneaked into the Capital City of Xichang
潜入首都西昌
to meet father at the silk shop,
在丝绸店见到父亲，
person by his side
他身边的人
is Lieutenant He.
是何中尉。
In addition,
此外，
Lieutenant He who helped the King of Qin
帮助秦​​王的何副将
plan the meeting.
计划会议。
The girl is graceful
女孩很优雅
and wise.
和明智的。
He makes a deep impression on people.
他 给人们留下了深刻的印象。
Apparently she is Cui Yi's daughter.
显然她是崔毅的女儿。
Wan'niang.
Wan'niang.
Dad knows
爸爸知道
you have big ambitions.
你有远大的抱负。
Considering Cui Lin
考虑到崔琳
Cui Yi's daughter,
崔毅的女儿，
King of Qin
秦王
maybe like him.
也许喜欢他。
Ayah
阿亚
will help me
会帮助我
You are so clever.
你真聪明。
Dad for sure
爸爸肯定
try your best
尽你所能
to help you
来帮你
Cui Yi's daughter is not great either.
崔毅的女儿也不出色。
His father
他的父亲
commander-in-chief wields military power.
总司令 行使军事权力。
My father too
我的父亲也是
chief civil servants.
首席公务员。
I just listen
我只是听
the emperor was afraid of the border officials
皇帝害怕边境官员
who holds military power,
谁拥有军事权力，
but never heard of it
但从未听说过
the emperor is afraid of
皇帝害怕
gentle civil servant.
温柔的公务员。
Good to say you.
很高兴说你。
Dad knows
爸爸知道
father's daughter
父亲的女儿
comparable to Cui Yi's daughter.
堪比崔毅的女儿。
The young lady looks beautiful in this kind of dress.
这位年轻女士 穿这种衣服看起来很漂亮。
I'm just worried
我只是担心
The young lady showed herself
这位年轻女士展现了自己
by wearing men's clothes.
通过穿男装。
With clothes like this,
有了这样的衣服，
will they feel
他们会觉得
not used to?
不习惯？
Now,
现在，
Dad already told everyone that
爸爸已经告诉大家了
I am his only daughter.
我是他唯一的女儿。
In that case,
在这种情况下，
I have to show
我必须展示
my stripes
我的条纹
As his daughter,
作为他的女儿，
I will definitely make him proud.
我一定会让他感到骄傲。
Hurry up and see.
快点去看看吧。
So beautiful.
如此美丽。
Your taste is good.
你的品味很好。
Very suitable for young lady's skin color.
非常适合小姐姐的肤色。
Li Ni greeted the commander-in-chief.
李妮向 总司令打招呼。
What business does the King of Qin have?
秦王有什么生意？
Still about the Changzhou clause.
还是关于常州条款。
I want to discuss the Changzhou clause
我想讨论一下常州条款
with the commander in chief.
与总司令。
The new King of Qin
新秦王
save me
救我
So,
所以，
did you come to demand revenge?
你是来要求报仇的吗？
I don't dare to do that.
我不敢这么做。
Who sent the letter?
这封信是谁寄来的？
to the Cui Family Army
致崔家军
to save Pei Yuan?
救裴渊？
King Qin still remembers, right?
秦王还记得吧？
The commander-in-chief held out his hand.
总司令伸出了手。
I am very grateful.
我很感激。
However, things have changed.
然而，事情已经发生了变化。
The great commander conquered Changzhou.
大统帅攻克常州。
Not only criticized by the government,
不仅受到政府的批评，
even the commander-in-chief needs to be wary of Sun Jing.
就算是统帅，也 需要警惕孙靖。
After all,
毕竟，
distance between Changzhou and Luoyang,
distance between Changzhou and Luoyang,
Jianzhou, Bingzhou
Jianzhou, Bingzhou
and a military camp in Pingliang
以及平凉的一个军营
quite far.
蛮远。
The Cui Family Army is here
崔家军来了
not even profitable.
甚至没有盈利。
do you mean
你的意思是
Changzhou
常州
useless
无用
for me,
为我，
is it ok if i return it to you?
我可以把它还给你吗？
Great Commander.
伟大的指挥官。
Why don't I change Luoyang and Changzhou
我为什么不换 洛阳和常州
dengan Weiyang?
dengan Weiyang?
What does King Qin mean?
秦王是什么意思？
Although Weiyang is not in my jurisdiction,
虽然未央不在 我管辖范围内，
Weiyang is located to the left of Pingliang.
未央位于 平凉左侧。
Civil and military affairs
文武事务
in my jurisdiction as Commander-in-Chief of Pingliang.
归我 担任平凉总司令管辖。
You want to exchange my stuff
你想交换我的东西
with my stuff?
和我的东西？
In fact, you theorized.
事实上，你已经推理了。
Commander-in-chief needs real rights.
总司令需要实权。
Although Weiyang is close to Pingliang,
Although Weiyang is close to Pingliang,
there is an army
有一支军队
the administrative center of Youzhou is based there.
幽州的行政中心 就设在那里。
If the hall gives a series of orders,
如果大厅发出一系列命令，
the great commander controlled Pingliang
大帅控制平凉
Dan Weiyang.
Dan Weiyang.
So, great commander
所以，伟大的指挥官
can control
可以控制
Pingliang's affairs
平凉事
and Weiyang officially.
正式与未央。
Later, the position of the Cui Family Army will be strong and there will be no worries.
以后崔家军的地位 就会稳固，就没有后顾之忧了。
What does the commander in chief think?
总司令怎么想？
In that case,
在这种情况下，
as long as the ballroom is a draw
只要舞厅平局
hand over Weiyang to me,
把未央交给我，
I will withdraw from Changzhou.
我将撤出常州。
However, I will not back down
然而我不会退缩
from Luoyang.
from Luoyang.
The commander-in-chief's mind was firm.
总司令的心思很坚定。
Even though I feel all wrong,
虽然我感觉一切都不对劲
I will ask the Balairung Seri to issue the order immediately.
我会要求Balairung Seri 立即发布命令。
I will only bring up Changzhou.
我只提常州。
Don't worry, commander in chief.
别担心，总司令。
Okay.
好的。
King of Qin.
秦王。
After the Changzhou clause was settled,
常州条款解决后，
you can go back to the capital.
你可以回首都了。
Great Commander.
伟大的指挥官。
I have one more request.
我还有一个请求。
What is he?
他是什么？
I would like to have Young Miss Cui lead the Cui Family Army
我想让崔小姐 统领崔家军
go to the Tong Border with me
跟我去潼边境
to eradicate Sun Jing.
铲除孙靖。
You want to ask my son
你想问我儿子
go against Sun Jing with you?
跟你一起对抗孙靖？
King of Qin.
秦王。
Your request
你的申请
too many.
太多。
If Sun Jing is not eradicated,
如果不铲除孙靖，
not only government officials,
不仅是政府官员，
even the commander-in-chief was worried.
连总司令都担心了。
Originally, the commander-in-chief
原来，总司令
led the army to the south waving the army flag.
挥舞着军旗率领大军 南下。
Now, the commander-in-chief is temporarily based in Changzhou
现在总指挥 暂驻常州
and defend Luoyang.
and defend Luoyang.
Of course, the audience is buzzing.
当然，观众也是一片哗然。
As long as the commander-in-chief agrees the Cui Family Army and me
只要总司令同意 我和崔家军
go to the Barrel Border
前往桶边界
to defeat Sun Jing and recapture the Tong Border,
击败孙敬 ，夺回潼境，
rumors in the draw hall
抽奖厅里的谣言
will end.
会停。
In fact, everyone
事实上，每个人
will praise the obedience of the commander-in-chief.
会赞扬总司令的服从。
What if I don't agree?
如果我不同意怎么办？
After I myself recaptured the Tong Border,
我自己 收复潼境后，
maybe a series hall
也许是一个系列大厅
will order me
会命令我
to fight with the commander-in-chief.
与总司令并肩作战。
Until then,
直到那时，
I can't refuse it.
我无法拒绝。
Hall series
大厅系列
will definitely recapture Dongdu first.
肯定会先夺回东都。
Try the King of Qin.
试试秦王。
I am
我是
never fought with the King of Qin.
从未与秦王交战过。
I would like to witness
我愿意见证
the arrangement of the army of the King of Qin.
秦王军队的布置。
I don't want to
我不想
hostile to the Cui Family Army.
与崔家军敌对。
The commander-in-chief knows too.
总司令也知道。
The border of Tong locks the two cities.
潼边境锁两城。
Besides the Barrel Border,
除了桶状边框外，
there is no other place to defend these two cities.
没有其他地方可以 保卫这两座城市。
As long as the commander-in-chief agreed to the Cui Family Army
只要总司令 同意崔家军
go to the Tong Border with me,
跟我去潼边，
suspicion of the government
对政府的怀疑
against the Cui Family Army will be reduced.
对崔家军的 打击将会减少。
Hopefully the commander-in-chief can fulfill this request.
希望总司令 能够满足这个要求。
In that case,
在这种情况下，
My son does not need to go with you.
我儿子不需要跟你一起去。
I went to the Tong Border with you.
我和你一起去了 潼边境。
Indeed so.
确实如此。
Before this, I discussed with Ying.
在此之前， 我曾与颖讨论过。
He told me.
他告诉我。
Great Commander
伟大的统帅
will definitely say so.
肯定会这么说。
I asked Ying if it was appropriate for me to answer.
我问瑛我是否适合回答。
Ying told me.
莹告诉我的。
Talk
讲话
he and I have reached an agreement.
我和他已经达成协议。
He is willing to go with me.
他愿意和我一起去。
If you have reached agreement,
如果你们已经达成协议，
why are you asking me again?
你为什么又问我？
Does this mean the commander-in-chief has agreed?
这是否意味着 总司令已经同意了？
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你，先生。
Who is your uncle?
你叔叔是谁？
Go away from here!
离开这里！
Of.
的。
Even though King Qin extended his hand this time,
尽管秦王 这次伸出了手，
Tentera Zhenxi
Tentera Zhenxi
still yearning for Changzhou.
依然向往常州。
We need to be vigilant.
我们需要保持警惕。
He is the emperor's son.
他是皇帝的儿子。
He came because he received orders.
他来是因为他接到命令。
We cannot cooperate with him so easily.
我们不能 这么轻易地与他合作。
Ying.
莹。
There are many men in this world.
这个世界上有很多男人。
Why do you admire him?
你为什么欣赏他？
Ayah.
呀呀。
He is worth my admiration.
他值得我敬佩。
It is difficult to predict the situation now.
现在很难预测情况。
Even though Sun Jing lost, he was still at the Tong Border.
孙敬虽然败了，但 他还在潼边。
The three princes compete with each other.
三位王子互相竞争。
The King of Qin has great merit and is easily overcome by problems.
秦王有大功 ，很容易被问题所克服。
Although King Qin is unmatched,
秦王虽无敌，
he is not an ideal partner.
他不是一个理想的合作伙伴。
Ying, you need to think hard
莹，你要好好想想
if you want to be with him.
如果你想和他在一起。
Ayah.
呀呀。
I like Li Ni.
就像李妮一样。
He likes me too.
他也喜欢我。
Although
虽然
there are many men in this world,
这个世界上有很多男人，
he's the only one
他是唯一的一个
can capture my heart.
能俘获我的心。
I only have you as a child.
我只有你一个孩子。
Since you've already thought about cooking
既然 你已经考虑过做饭了
and make decisions,
并做出决定，
I won't try to change your mind.
我不会试图改变你的想法。
Thank you dad.
谢谢爸爸。
Mari.
马里。
- Drink.
- 喝。
The young lady is educated and willing to fight.
这位年轻女士受过教育 ，愿意战斗。
In fact, she is the daughter of the great commander.
事实上， 她是大统帅的女儿。
In your opinion,
依你的意见，
who is worthy
谁值得
be his partner?
成为他的伙伴？
In my opinion,
在我看来，
The King of Qin suits.
秦王正服。
Since saving the emperor,
自从救了皇帝之后，
King Qin led the Zhenxi Army and never lost.
秦王率领镇西军 ，从未失利。
Put other things aside.
其他的事情先放在一边。
He is a rare commander-in-chief
他是一位罕见的统帅
in the war on the Tong Border.
在潼边的战争中。
Although King Qin was brilliant,
秦王虽然才华横溢，
he is the emperor's son.
他是皇帝的儿子。
Miss
错过
should take a husband.
应该找个丈夫。
That's right.
这是正确的。
She should take a husband.
她应该找个丈夫。
Mari.
马里。
did you hear
你听到了吗
They think
他们认为
only i match you
只有我配得上你
I just heard them say
我刚刚听到他们说
I should take my husband.
我应该带我的丈夫。
As a prince,
作为一个王子，
are you willing to marry and live in the Cui Family?
你愿意嫁到 崔家生活吗？
♪The sky is full of color♪
♪天空充满色彩♪
The so-called Prince or King of Qin.
所谓的太子或者秦王。
I don't want to hold either of these positions and I don't even care.
我不想担任 这两个职位，我什至不在乎。
Ying, let's go back to the Laolan Border.
莹，我们回老兰边境去吧。
We got married there and gave birth to seven or eight children.
我们在那里结婚并生了 七八个孩子。
Half of them go by your last name.
其中一半 以您的姓氏命名。
Others go by my last name.
其他人都以我的姓氏命名。
I am not married and you are not married.
我没有结婚 ，你也没有结婚。
You don't marry and I don't live in the Cui Residence.
你不嫁 ，我也不住崔宅。
Good?
好的？
Dream it.
做梦。
Who wants to give birth to seven or eight children with you?
谁愿意跟你生七八 个孩子？
Then, four people.
然后是四个人。
At least four people.
至少有四个人。
Two children follow the surname Cui.
两个孩子 都姓崔。
Others go by the surname Li.
其他人都姓李。
What kind of?
什么样的？
If you're bullshitting again,
如果你又胡言乱语
I will rip your mouth off.
我会把你的嘴撕掉。
Do you want to tear my mouth?
你想撕破我的嘴吗？
Of.
的。
Dream it.
做梦。
♪I miss you forever♪
♪我永远想念你♪
♪I'm willing to give up this world for you♪
♪我愿意为你放弃这个世界 ♪
♪There are no regrets in this life♪
♪此生无悔♪
Fear not, Your Highness.
不要害怕，殿下。
Fifth Han.
第五何。
It's been so long.
已经过去这么久了。
Siege, pursuit, contest of wisdom and courage.
攻城、追击、 智慧与勇气的较量。
You manage to escape every time.
每次你都设法逃脱。
Fortunately yesterday
幸运的是昨天
We didn't chase you in Huayang Week on purpose
华阳周我们不是故意追你的
so that you remember here is safe
让你记住这里是安全的
and we managed to surround you.
我们成功包围了你。
Fifth Han.
第五何。
The governor respects you for your obedience.
州长尊重你 的服从。
As long as you hand over his great-grandson,
只要交出他的曾孙，
you will not die
你不会死的
Protect his great-grandson even if he dies!
就算死也要保护他的曾孙！
Attack!
攻击！
Watch out for Commander Han's back!
小心韩司令的背影！
Fifth Han!
第五他！
Honourable!
尊敬的！
Go quickly!
快去！
Fifth Han!
第五他！
Road!
路！
Honourable!
尊敬的！
Fifth Han!
第五他！
It's useless.
没用的。
Let me go!
让我走！
Fifth Han!
第五他！
Honourable!
尊敬的！
Honourable.
尊敬的。
Fifth Han!
第五他！
Governor.
州长。
Li Xuanze.
Li Xuanze.
Say hello to the governor.
向州长问好。
You're the rebel who killed the emperor!
你就是弑君的叛徒！
Barbaric!
野蛮！
Stop!
停止！
Don't scare him.
别吓到他。
Han Chang hid you for so long.
韩畅 把你藏了这么久。
At a critical moment,
在关键时刻，
he still failed to protect you, didn't he?
他还是没能保护好你不是吗？
Even if he obeys,
就算他听从了，
he could not resist the letter of destiny.
他无法抗拒命运之书。
Honourable.
尊敬的。
The letter to the King of Qin has been sent?
给秦王的信已经发出了？
Has been sent by speed horse.
已被快马送去。
Don't worry, Your Highness.
别担心，殿下。
King Qin must have tried to save his great-grandson.
秦王一定是想 救他的曾孙。
Although Sun Jin managed to capture his great-grandson,
孙晋虽然 擒获了他的曾孙，
I feel
我觉得
he wouldn't mind his great-grandson so soon.
他不会介意 他的曾孙这么快就来了。
May we still have time to save his great-grandson.
愿我们还有时间 拯救他的曾孙。
Commander Han has already spoken.
韩司令已经发话了。
He reorganized the rest of his army.
他重组了剩余的军队。
He will try to save his great-grandson as well.
他也会尽力 拯救他的曾孙。
His great-grandson is blessed by God.
他的曾孙受到上帝的祝福。
He will definitely survive.
他一定会活下来。
(Dewan Chaoqian)
(Dewan Chaoqian)
Why my lord?
为什么我的主？
sent down the order
下订单
to rebuke King Qin?
斥责秦王？
Beta ordered him to Changzhou to solve the problem.
贝塔命令他去 常州解决问题。
He too
他也是
forced beta
强制贝塔
bestow the title
授予称号
Panglima Besar Weiyang kepada Cui Yi.
Panglima Besar Weiyang kepada Cui Yi.
In fact, he said
事实上，他说
the Luoyang clause has become a reality
洛阳条款已成为现实
and don't bring it up for a while.
并且暂时不要提起它。
Itu Dongdu.
Itu Dongdu.
He considered the affairs of the country
他考虑国家大事
as buying and selling.
作为买卖。
He also reported that
他还报道说
after the Changzhou problem is solved,
常州问题解决后，
he and the Cui Family Army
他和崔家军
will go to recapture the Tong Border.
将会去夺回潼边境。
The Cui Family Army was ambitious.
崔家军野心勃勃。
What kind of
什么样的
if they colluded
如果他们串通
dengan Sun Jing?
dengan Sun Jing?
my lord
我的主
This was agreed in a meeting in the seri court.
这是 在法庭的一次会议上达成一致的。
Considering Weiyang
Considering Weiyang
indeed in Cui Yi's jurisdiction,
确实在崔毅的管辖范围内，
It is good that my lord bestowed this title on him.
陛下 授予他这个称号是件好事。
Rumor has it, His Majesty issued an order
传闻，陛下下达了命令
to rebuke you.
来斥责你。
I already guessed that your father would reprimand me,
我已经猜到 你父亲会训斥我了
but I didn't think this would happen so quickly.
但我没想到 这会发生得这么快。
Even if you finish
就算你完成了
Changzhou problem without war,
没有战争的常州问题，
but the title of Grand Commander of Weiyang was given to someone else.
但未央太尉的称号 却被别人赐予了。
In fact, you promised not to bring up Luoyang.
其实你答应过 不提洛阳的。
Isn't this the title of the trial
这不是审判的标题吗
to your enemy in the draw?
在平局中给你的敌人？
If I were them,
如果我是他们，
I will criticize you too.
我也会批评你。
You
你
great service in the war.
在战争中做出了伟大的贡献。
Most military officers
大多数军官
in the hall series comes from the Zhenxi Army.
馆系列中 出自镇西军。
Of course they will be on your side.
他们当然 会站在你这边。
If not,
如果不，
you are not just reprimanded.
你不只是被训斥。
Instead, your position as King of Qin will be stripped.
相反，你的 秦王之位将会被剥夺。
I do not care.
我不在乎。
After all.
毕竟。
After recapturing the Tong Border,
收复塘边境后，
I will return to the Laolan Border.
我将返回老兰边境。
It's better than being bullied by people in the draw.
总比抽签时被人欺负好。
Maybe you can't go back to Laolan Border
也许你回不去 老兰边境了
after recapturing the Tong Border.
收复潼边境后。
Not necessarily.
不必要。
Tuan Shiqi.
Tuan Shiqi.
There was an immediate report from Concubine Xiao.
萧妃立刻传来了报告。
He said, Sun Jing had already held his great-grandson.
他说，孙敬 已经抱着他的曾孙了。
What?
什么？
Report!
报告！
Immediate report from the Tong border.
潼边即时报告。
Sun Jing issued a notice of rebellion
孙敬发出 叛变通知
at the Tong Border in the name of his great-grandson.
以他曾孙的名义在潼边。
His great-grandson?
他的曾孙？
Of.
的。
Rebel Sun has found his great-grandson.
叛逆太阳 找到了他的曾孙。
In the notice,
通知中，
he criticized...
他批评...
Talk!
讲话！
He criticized my lord the illegitimate emperor.
他批评我主 是私生子。
and called for the army that saved the emperor
并呼吁军队 拯救皇帝
in the name of his great-grandson to eliminate the illegitimate emperor
以曾孙之名 消灭私生子皇帝
so that his great-grandson can ascend the throne.
以便他的曾孙能够登上王位。
Your father.
你的父亲。
Since Sun Jing was defeated and withdrew,
自从孙敬兵败退走后，
he has no more effort.
他已经没有力气了。
No one knows
没人知道
in case his great-grandson is his real great-great-grandson.
万一他的曾孙 是他真正的曾曾孙。
Patik suggested
帕蒂克建议
we find a boy and claim that he is his great grandson.
我们找到一个男孩 并声称他是他的曾孙。
No one can distinguish who is his real great-grandson.
谁是他真正的曾孙，谁也分不清。
Honourable,
尊敬的，
Sun Jing dared to issue a notice,
孙静敢于发出通知，
apparently he could prove the boy's identity.
显然他可以证明 这个男孩的身份。
If we look for a fake great-grandson of his majesty,
如果我们要找 一个陛下的假曾孙，
this will be
这会是
people laugh
人们笑
and harm us?
并伤害我们？
What is Sun Jing's evidence that can prove the boy's identity?
孙静有什么证据可以 证明男孩的身份？
In Sun Jing's notice,
在孙静的通知中，
His great-grandson brought
他的曾孙带来了
seal of the late crown prince.
已故皇太子的印章。
my lord
我的主
Sun Jing questioned the legitimacy of this kingdom in the name of his great-grandson.
孙敬 以曾孙的名义质疑这个王国的合法性。
This is unforgivable.
这是不可原谅的。
Now,
现在，
whether his great-grandson is true or not,
不管他的曾孙 是真是假，
we should send an army to fight against Sun Jing,
应该派兵 去讨伐孙敬，
restore the Tong Border and his great-grandson.
恢复 潼边和他的曾孙。
In my opinion,
在我看来，
King Qin once recaptured the Tong Border
秦王曾 收复潼境
and fought with Sun Jing repeatedly.
并与 孙敬屡次交手。
Furthermore, King Qin proposed to crack down on the Sun Rebels.
此外，秦王还提出 要镇压太阳叛军。
So, King of Qin
那么，秦王
the most suitable candidate to go to war.
最适合 参战的人选。
In that case, order the King of Qin to lead the army
既然如此，就命令秦王 率军吧
go fight the Sun Rebels and recapture the Tong Border.
去对抗太阳叛军 ，夺回塘边境。
Doesn't he love to fight?
他不是很爱打架吗？
This time, he can fight to his heart's content.
这一次，他可以 尽情战斗了。
(Boundary Barrel)
（边界桶）
Sun Jing issued a notice of rebellion
孙敬发出 叛变通知
to delay time on behalf of the military forces attacking Baiyue.
拖延时间代表 大军攻打百越。
Actually, the strength of the army defending the Tong Border is not enough.
事实上，潼边的守军兵力还不够。
Do you have a plan?
你有计划吗？
to take the opportunity to attack into the Tong Border?
趁机 攻入潼境？
How do you know that I already have a plan?
你怎么知道 我已经有计划了？
It's easy to defend the Tong Border, but it's hard to attack it.
守潼边易， 攻潼边难。
However, you once attacked
然而，你曾经攻击过
Bind border by force.
以武力束缚边界。
Then, quite a while Zhenxi Army
然后，好一阵子镇西军
defending the Tong Border.
保卫潼边。
According to your nature,
根据你的本性，
you must be watching
你一定在看
conditions outside and inside the boundary carefully.
仔细检查边界内外的情况 。
Of.
的。
I left
我离开了
a secret passage in the Tong Border.
潼边境的一条秘密通道。
Secret passage?
秘密通道？
Is it a ditch?
是沟吗？
How do you know?
你怎么知道？
The texture of the soil Border Tong is hard.
边塘土壤质地坚硬。
If you want to dig a tunnel,
如果你想挖隧道
not easy either.
也不容易。
So, this secret passage
那么，这条秘密通道
not newly built.
不是新建的。
It has been around for a long time
它已经存在很长时间了
and you can use it.
你可以使用它。
As I remember, in the Ruijing Year,
我记得，瑞景年，
The Tong border was once hit by a flash flood.
潼边境 曾遭遇山洪暴发。
The military armory was flooded with water.
军械库被水淹没。
Then, the Ministry of Finance allocates money
然后财政部 拨款
to repair the ditch.
来修复沟渠。
The ditch was quite deep and wide.
那条沟又深又宽。
It feels like people can move inside.
感觉人可以进去。
You know about
你知道
the affairs of the Ministry of Finance in the Year of Ruijing?
瑞景年财政部的事？
Childhood,
童年，
I like to read with my father.
我喜欢和爸爸一起读书。
In his reading room,
在他的阅览室里，
besides books about the military,
除了军事方面的书籍，
there are also many files
还有很多文件
about repairs
关于维修
which is conducted at all borders.
这是在所有边境进行的。
I read it as a story book.
我把它当作一本故事书来读。
I remember it after reading.
读完我就记住了。
Tonight...
今晚...
Tonight, King of Qin
今夜，秦王
will be rats that infiltrate the ditch.
将会有老鼠 潜入沟渠。
Of course I have to accompany you.
我当然要陪你。
I will await your instructions outside the city.
我会 在城外等待你的指示。
♪If you've forgotten the twinkling light♪
♪如果你忘记了闪烁的光芒♪
♪Tunggu kenangan♪
♪东古肯南甘♪
♪Shattered and sunk♪
♪破碎沉没♪
♪The spots that remain on your heart♪
♪留在心中的斑点♪
♪Penarikan itu♪
♪佩纳里坎伊图♪
♪It's my objection♪
♪我反对♪
♪If longing is never left behind♪
♪如果渴望不被遗忘的话♪
♪Longing to go back to the earliest times♪
♪渴望回到 最初的时光♪
♪The warmth that fate once had♪
♪命运曾经拥有的温暖 ♪
♪I want to keep it for you♪
♪我想为你保留它♪
♪If love still remembers♪
♪如果爱还记得♪
♪We once promised♪
♪我们曾经约定♪
♪Even though love hurts me♪
♪尽管爱让我受伤♪
♪I must live for you too♪
♪我也必须为你而活♪
♪Following faces in memories♪
♪追随记忆中的面孔♪
♪Waiting is my obsession♪
♪等待是我的痴迷♪
♪If love still remembers♪
♪如果爱还记得♪
♪A promise kept for you♪
♪对你的承诺♪
♪Terbalikkan karma♪
♪Terbalikkan 因果报应♪
♪Loving for you without regret♪
♪爱你无怨无悔♪
♪I'm willing to leave it for you♪
♪我愿意把它留给你♪
♪I'm always waiting for you to answer me♪
♪我一直在等你 回答我♪
♪If love still remembers♪
♪如果爱还记得♪
♪A promise kept for you♪
♪对你的承诺♪
♪Terbalikkan karma♪
♪Terbalikkan 因果报应♪
♪Loving for you without regret♪
♪爱你无怨无悔♪
♪I'm willing to leave it for you♪
♪我愿意把它留给你♪
♪I'm always waiting for you to answer me♪
♪我一直在等你 回答我♪